module.exports = [
  {
    prompt: 'Milwaukee has a famous statue of which character(s)?',
    choices: [
      'Steve Urkel (Family Matters)',
      'The Fonz (Happy Days)',
      'Laverne & Shirley (Laverne & Shirley)',
      "Red (That 70's show)",
    ],
    answer: 'The Fonz (Happy Days)',
  },
  {
    prompt: 'Wisconsin holds the US (lower-48) record for which of the following?',
    choices: [
      'Most lakes',
      'Highest dairy production',
      'Most cows per capita',
      'Oldest standing barn',
    ],
    answer: 'Most lakes',
  },
  {
    prompt: "Wisconsin is home to America's...",
    choices: [
      'Largest music festival',
      'Largest water park',
      'Oldest bowling alley',
      'Oldest soccer team',
      'All of the above',
    ],
    answer: 'All of the above',
  },
  {
    prompt: 'Where does the nickname Kiermo Bean come from?',
    choices: ['', '', '', ''],
    answer: 'Seth in Taco Bell',
  },
  {
    prompt: 'What were the first sports we played?',
    choices: ['', '', '', ''],
    answer: 'Baseball and soccer',
  },
  {
    prompt: "What is Zach's nickname for his sister?",
    choices: ['Butter', 'Nikki', 'Smidge', 'Little'],
    answer: 'Smidge',
  },
  {
    prompt: "Who was Kierstyn's first high school boyfriend?",
    choices: ['', '', '', ''],
    answer: 'Josh',
  },
  {
    prompt: 'What instrument did Zach play in band?',
    choices: ['', '', '', ''],
    answer: 'Trumpet',
  },
  {
    prompt: "What was Kierstyn's original college major?",
    choices: ['', '', '', ''],
    answer: '',
  },
  {
    prompt: 'What street did Zach and Scott live on in college?',
    choices: ['', '', '', ''],
    answer: 'Water',
  },
  {
    prompt: 'Who does Kierstyn have a matching ribcage tattoo with?',
    choices: ['Britni', 'Sierra', 'Erica', 'Kaia'],
    answer: '',
  },
  {
    prompt: 'How many baseball stadiums has Zach been to?',
    choices: ['', '', '', ''],
    answer: '',
  },
  {
    prompt: 'Where did Zach and Kierstyn meet?',
    choices: [
      'Tinder',
      'Work',
      'Bumble',
      'The grocery store',
      'A bar',
      'A baseball game',
      'School',
    ],
    answer: 'Work',
  },
  {
    prompt: 'What product did Zach and Kierstyn work on together?',
    choices: ['GLAS', 'Metasys', 'NS 8000', 'Bright Cellars'],
    answer: 'GLAS',
  },
  {
    prompt: "Which of Zach and Kierstyn's friends can hang?",
    choices: ['Jon', 'Scott', 'Sierra', 'NOT Matt'],
    answer: 'NOT Matt',
  },
  {
    prompt: 'How many states have Zach and Kierstyn celebrated Thanksgiving in?',
    choices: ['One', 'Two', 'Three', 'Four'],
    answer: 'Three',
  },
  {
    prompt: "What is Kierstyn's favorite Milwaukee bar?",
    choices: ['Brothers', 'Boone and Crockett', '1840', 'Sugar Maple'],
    answer: 'Boone and Crockett',
  },
  {
    prompt: "What was Kierstyn's first tattoo?",
    choices: ['', '', '', ''],
    answer: '',
  },
  {
    prompt: 'How many tattoos does Kierstyn have?',
    choices: ['Six', 'Ten', 'Fourteen', 'Sixteen'],
    answer: '',
  },
  {
    prompt: "In school, what was Zach's favorite and Kierstyn's least favorite subject?",
    choices: ['Gym', 'Recess', 'Science', 'Math'],
    answer: 'Math',
  },
  // {
  //   prompt: 'What last name will Zach & Kierstyn Share?',
  //   choices: ['Oliv√≠ar', 'Olivare', 'Ahlivare', 'Olivair'],
  //   answer: 'Olivare',
  // },
]
